Guide to the Junior League of Brooklyn records ARC.304
Brooklyn Historical Society
- Series 11: Artifacts, 1985-2000; 22164
  - "Popcorn," ZEA, VHS, undated; 22200 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - "Power of Association," AJLI, VHS, undated; 22201 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - "Power of Association," AJLI, VHS (2), undated; 22202 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - "Project: Response to Rape," VHS (2), undated; 22203 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - "Project: Response to Rape," VHS (2), undated; 22204 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - "Restoring Dignity," VHS (2), undated; 22205 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - "Very Special Arts," Amway Corporation, VHS, undated; 22206 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - "Woman to Woman" public service announcements, magnetic (2), undated; 22207 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - "Woman to Woman" public service announcements, magnetic large, undated; 22208 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - "Woman to Woman" public service announcements, magnetic large, undated; 22209 (Box 29, Folder 11)